[{"id": 842, "question": "Individuality is the particular character, or aggregate (total) of qualities that distinguishes one person or thing from others. Many artists late in the last century were in search of a means to express their individuality. Modern dance was one of the ways some of these people sought to free their creative spirit. At the beginning there was no exacting technique, no foundation from which to build. In later years, trial, error and genius founded the techniques and the principles of the movement. Eventually, innovators even drew from what they considered the dread ballet, but first they had to get rid of all that was academic so that the new could be discovered. The beginnings of modern dance were happening before Isadora Duncan, but she was the first person to bring the new dance to genera...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that the author   _  .", "options": ["appreciates modern dance very much", "dislikes Isadora Duncan's dance", "thinks highly of individuality", "knows a lot about modern arts"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 109, "question": "Ariau Amazon Towers The Ariau Amazon Towers hotel lets you sleep in a tree house. Eight towers make up this hotel that offers over 300 rooms. If you really want to get into the spirit, book the Tarzan Suite which is large enough for a big family. You'll be thirty feet up in the air and can travel between the towers through their wooden walkways. Prices: starting at $300 one night for each person for a regular room and going all the way up to $3000 for the Tarzan Suite. For more information, visit the website: http://www.ariautowers.com The Ice Hotel Every winter in Jukkasjarvi, Sweden, a special kind of hotel called the Ice Hotel is built. Each year, world-famous artists are invited to design and produce works of art from the ice, many of which can be found in the rooms. You'll have your c...\n\nQ: Which hotel would invite artists to come to work every year?", "options": ["Propeller Island City Lodge.", "Ariau Amazon Towers.", "The Ice Hotel.", "Bahama Beach Club."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2012, "question": "Japan' s nuclear crisis is also causing concerns in China. Worried shoppers rushed to stores and supermarkets in the country for salt, with the belief that it might protect them from potential nuclear radiation spreading from Japan. Many rushed to buy to store as much iodized salt as possible because of the rumor that iodized salt could help prevent radiation poisoning spreading from Japan' s Fukushima Daiichi power plant. Consumers also worried that the nuclear plumes might spread to China by air and sea, polluting food sources, including salt taken from the sea. The wave of panic buying spread quickly across the country, driving up salt prices by five to ten fold in some cities. Even regions rich in salt production, like Jiangxi Province,faced sudden shortages. The government took measur...\n\nQ: What measures did the government take for the panic buying?", "options": ["Enough salt would be offered to each house.", "It admitted that salt could stop nuclear radiation.", "Authorities urged state-owned salt companies to increase the supply.", "Those who spread the rumor were all arrested and punished."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2603, "question": "Eighteen-year-old Dana Kiger is happily running after balls on the soccer field. But not long ago, she couldn't remember her love of the game, her parents' faces or even her name. At 16, the Tennessee honor student and star athlete was hit from behind while playing in a soccer game. She fell to the ground, her head striking the hard ground. The blow knocked out nearly all of Kiger's memories. With no physical injury or unusual change in her brain, doctors thought Kiger's memory would return in a few days. But it did not. And two and a half years later, it still hasn't. Kiger--who has no memory of her family, her childhood or her life before her injury--has had to create new memories, restart relationships and relearn old skills. \"The only thing I had ...I could walk, write, but I didn't kn...\n\nQ: From the dialogue between Kiger and her mother, we can infer that  _  .", "options": ["life was new to Kiger", "her family were united", "her mother was positive", "Kiger liked eating lettuce"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3492, "question": "Have you ever suddenly felt that someone you knew was in trouble--and was he? Have you ever dreamed something that came true later? Maybe you have ESP . ESP stands for Extra Sensory Perception. It may be called a sixth sense. It seems to let people know about events before they happen, or events that are happening some distance away. Here's an example. A woman was ironing clothes. Suddenly she screamed, \"My father is dead! I saw him sitting in the chair!\" Just then, a telegram came. The woman's father died of a heart attack. He died sitting in a chair. There are thousands of stories like this one on record. Scientists are studying them to find out what's behind these strange mental messages. Here's another example--one of hundreds of dreams that have come true: A man dreamed he was walking...\n\nQ: This article is mainly about  _  .", "options": ["the human dream", "the sixth sense", "the human mind", "a crowded bus"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 73, "question": "A new study has been carried to test the role of story telling in lowering blood pressure. Dr. Thomas Houston, a professor of the University of Massachusetts Medical School, led a group of scientists that investigated how pre-recorded videos of hypertension patients' talking about their medical histories helped another group of patients with high blood pressure to control their condition over several months. Houston was surprised by their studies that suggested that communication can be a powerful tool in medicine. They showed that those who had had similar experiences, when talking to someone with a similar background, could help change their behavior to become healthier. Hypertension is difficult to control, since it is dependent on diet, exercise and mental state. Medical treatments wit...\n\nQ: Which of the following could be the best title of the text?", "options": ["The stories of some hypertension patients.", "Medical treatments of blood pressure.", "Storytelling may help lower blood pressure.", "Suggestions about how to lower blood pressure."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1530, "question": "Conventional wisdom is a major barrier to innovation that threatens the survival of companies everywhere.It's based on the assumption that old ideas will always work,so they shouldn't be challenged. While this may be a valid assumption in situations that don't change,it's unlikely to hold true in a changing situation.In today's rapid changing global environment,old methods often don't work,and stubbornly using them can lead to major problems. Most people seem to agree with conventional wisdom because it gives one a false sense of security.If everyone else believes it,then it must be true.Individuals who use conventional wisdom are certain that they are right,and being right is good. They want to continue using old ideas rather than take risks with changes that might not work.In 1977,Ken Ol...\n\nQ: DEC has disappeared probably because   _  .", "options": ["the consumers didn't like its products", "the leaders lacked the sense of security", "the CEO stuck to the conventional ideas", "the employees took many risks with changes"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2970, "question": "My father, at the death of his father, was six years old, and he grew up without education. He moved from Kentucky to Indiana when I was seven. We reached our new home about the time the state came into the Union. It was a wild area, with many bears and other wild animals still in the woods. I grew up there. There were some so-called schools, but what was required of a teacher never went beyond \"reading, writing, and adding.\" If a stranger supposed to understand Latin happened to live for a time in the area, he was looked on as wizard . There was simply nothing to excite a desire for education. Of course, when I grew up, I did not know much. Still, somehow, I could read, write, and add, but that was all. The advance I have now made is on this store of education, which I have picked up unde...\n\nQ: When the writer was a child   _  .", "options": ["his grandfather died in the state of Kentucky", "his family settled down in the countryside of Indiana", "Kentucky joined the Union as a member state", "his family had to move from place to place"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3113, "question": "Then comes July, and with it examinations, but these are soon finished and with them ends the school year. Boys and girls have nearly two months' holiday before them as they leave school by train and car to return home to their fathers and mothers. The summer holidays are the best part of the year for most children. The weather is usually good, so that one can spend most of one's time playing in the garden or, if one lives in the country, out in the woods and fields. Even if one lives in a big town, one can usually go to a park to play. The best place for a summer holiday, however, is the seaside. Some children are lucky enough to live near the sea, but for the others who do not, a week or two at one of the big seaside towns is something that they will talk about for the whole of the follo...\n\nQ: July and August are the brightest months for most children, for they can  _  .", "options": ["stay with their parents for all the vacation.", "do more reading", "play out-of-door", "meet their old friends"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 843, "question": "Individuality is the particular character, or aggregate (total) of qualities that distinguishes one person or thing from others. Many artists late in the last century were in search of a means to express their individuality. Modern dance was one of the ways some of these people sought to free their creative spirit. At the beginning there was no exacting technique, no foundation from which to build. In later years, trial, error and genius founded the techniques and the principles of the movement. Eventually, innovators even drew from what they considered the dread ballet, but first they had to get rid of all that was academic so that the new could be discovered. The beginnings of modern dance were happening before Isadora Duncan, but she was the first person to bring the new dance to genera...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Artists of the Last Century", "Evolution of Dance in the 20th Century", "Natural Movement in Dance", "A Pioneer in Modern Dance"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2482, "question": "We live in a dangerous world. The figures for crime go up year by year. If you were attacked in the street, would you be able to defend yourself? Not very well probably, especially if someone was pointing a gun at you. We all see a lot of violence of films, but recently some programs on television showed how people can defend themselves without guns. For example, in one film a woman was attacked from behind. She threw the man, who was heavier and stronger than she was, over her head. Then she held him tightly on the ground. How? She knew Judo. Jiu-jitsu, as judo is sometimes called, means \"muscle science\" in Japanese. The student of judo needs to learn a lot about the body, its bones and muscles. Judo uses a number of \"falls\", \"holds\" and \"throws\". Someone who does not know judo cannot def...\n\nQ: If a man knows judo, he   _  .", "options": ["will be good at muscle science.", "will be able to avoid being attacked from his back.", "may defeat any strong person.", "can help himself by using the other person's body"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2943, "question": "Johnson went to Penquay for the weekend. He arrived there late on Friday evening. The landlady of the guest house, Mrs. Smith, answered the door and showed him to his room. Johnson was very tired and went straight to bed. He slept well and didn't wake up until nine o'clock the next morning. Johnson went downstairs for breakfast. Because there were no other guests, Mrs. Smith invited him to have breakfast with her family. Her only daughter, Catherine, about 13, was already sitting in the dining-room. Mrs. Smith went to the kitchen to prepare breakfast. Johnson noticed there were four places at the table and asked Catherine if there was another guest. Catherine told him that it was an empty place. And it used to be her father's place. Her father had been a fisherman. Three years before he ha...\n\nQ: Why did Mrs. Smith invite Johnson to have breakfast with her family?", "options": ["He woke up too late for his breakfast.", "There was an empty place at the table.", "He was the only guest on that day.", "Her daughter wanted to talk with him."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2825, "question": "Martha had been working for Miller Laboratories for two years, but she was not happy there. Nothing significant had happened in the way of promotions or salary increases. Martha felt that her supervisor, a younger and less experienced person than she, did not like her. In fact, the supervisor often said unpleasant things to her. One day, while talking with her friend Maria, she mentioned how discouraged she was. Maria gave her the name of a cousin of hers who was director of Human Resources Department for a large chemical company. Martha called him the next day and set up an interview on her lunch hour. During the interview, Mr. Petri said, \"You're just the kind of person we need here. You're being wasted in your other job. Give me a call in a day or two. I'm sure we can find a place for y...\n\nQ: What does Maria think of Martha's decision?", "options": ["Martha has handled the matter properly.", "Martha shouldn't have set the bridge on fire.", "Martha should have found a new job before leaving.", "Martha shouldn't have lost her temper with her supervisor"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1179, "question": "Scientists have exactly discovered the set of brain cells involved in making risky decisions, and have been able to control them in rats using targeted light. By changing the activity of the cells they were able to change the behaviour of risk-taking rats to avoid risk, hinting the approach could in future be used to treat people with impulse control problems. Risk-taking is a key part of survival, knowing when to take a chance could pay off--such as moving to a new area to look for food when pickings are slim. While all animals need an element of risk, the preference towards it varies between individuals. Researchers found this variation, which determines how risk-averse an individual is, is regulated by brain cells in a region of the brain called the nucleus accumbens. This cluster of ne...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from what Professor Karl Deisseroth said?", "options": ["Humans and rats differ in their preference for risk-taking.", "Too much risk-taking can do more harm than good.", "Risk-taking can be used to treat people with impulse control problems.", "Risk-taking is a means of survival and brings higher returns to humans."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 506, "question": "I am so worried about global warming. We need stop cutting down all of the trees so that they can absorb the carbon dioxide. I think the Kyoto Protocol to stop pollution is a great idea ,and I hope our country will decide to follow it, too.[: http://wx.jtyjy.com/] -- Eli S.,10,Texa People should do all they can to help stop pollution, even if it is something as little as recycling your soda can. Every little thing helps. Maybe schools can put recycling bins in classrooms. Students can bring in all of their cans and bottles and see how many the school can collect. -- Lindsey A.,11, Massachusett[: http://wx.jtyjy.com/.Com] The United States should take action to help stop pollution. Since we are one of the richest countries, we should at least spend a little money to help. -- Aaron z,11,Mass...\n\nQ: Why does Lindsey suggest schools put recycling bins in classrooms?", "options": ["To keep the classroom clean", "To help protect wild animals.", "To help protect our earth.", "To collect waste in classroom."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3398, "question": "Women love shoes! They will sometimes go to look for the perfect pair of shoes to wear only once with the perfect outfit or the fashion of the day. Once worn, these fashionable designer shoes may spend weeks, months, or years in the closet without being worn again until another special occasion comes up. With that said, are expensive designer shoes really worth their cost? Historically, shoes were invented to free feet from sharp rocks, hot sands, and blisters. Shoes were made to be simple and functional, with tough leather soles and straps. As society became more sophisticated , the role of shoes changed; shoes were made to add status to the wearer. Shoe designers began to work on the production of fashion shoes for the wealthy; shoes meant more for show than for practical use or simplici...\n\nQ: Designer shoes will remain on the market because they   _  .", "options": ["make a lot of money for shoemakers", "meet women's demand for being special", "will become increasingly comfortable", "offer the wearer a chance to show off their wealth"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2664, "question": "Try imagining what the world will be like in the year 3000. Some serious thinkers are starting to imagine just that. Bart: I don't know that present-day electronic chips are, but some sort of chips -- I'd guess maybe plastic. Our three-pound brain is definitely a wonder, perhaps the greatest wonder of natural biology. In this coming century, we'll be re-engineering the brain a piece at a time, first with implants and finally engineering an complete replacement. There's no question that in the distant future we'll play the music of the mind on instruments different from the current ones. So, yes, chips are our destiny . Edward: In 3000 perhaps the biggest difference from today is that there will be no more men. Females can have female children, without any need for men. In about ten years, ...\n\nQ: In 3000, what about the population of the world?", "options": ["It will be all made up of females.", "It will be larger than that of present.", "It will mainly consists of children.", "It will be reduced by a drink of cocktail."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2745, "question": "Many of you may wonder what else to do besides watching TV or surfing the Internet on weekends.Why not have a picnic? Junior 2 students at Beijing No.4 Middle Schoo1 had a \"King of cooking\" competition* Earlier this month,about 300 students at the schoo1 went to a suburb of Beijing to have the contest.They were divided into 24 groups.Each group had buyers,slicers ,firemakers.washers and cooks. Firemakers faced the most problems during the time.Some of them had no idea how to keep fire burning. \"The fire kept going out.we had to blow at the sparks and put on corn leaves and old newspapers,\"said Wu Mofei,13. \"It took us an hour to make the fire.Our eyes had tears from all the smoke and our faces became dirty,\"he added. When the fires were finally made,the cooks became the busiest people.Huan...\n\nQ: The text mainly tells us----.", "options": ["a \"King of Cooking\" competition organized by Senior 2 students at Beijing No.4 Middle School", "a picnic organized by Junior 2 students at Beijing N0.4 Middle School", "a \"King of Cooking\" competition organized by Junior 2 students at Beijing No.4 Middle School", "after-school activities of students at Beijing No.4 Middlle School"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3052, "question": "One warm September night, Mira had come down to the beach to enjoy the night air. She closed her eyes and listened to the waves. Suddenly, she could hear another sound, so she opened her eyes and looked down at the sand. It was moving! All of a sudden she could see a tiny head coming out. Then a turtle appeared! One by one they struggled out of their underground nests. Mira looked in surprise at the baby turtles. Mira knew the turtles should head towards the waves and swim away, so she was puzzled when they began to pull themselves towards the dunes . Suddenly, she remembered something her grandmother had told her. \"Sea turtles bury their eggs on the beach every year in April and in September. Those baby turtles hatch and head back down to the sea. But some of them never make it. Sometimes...\n\nQ: How did Mira feel when she saw the baby turtles appear?", "options": ["Proud.", "Sad.", "Confused.", "Surprised."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2488, "question": "They tell us when to get up or when we're running late for work and whether we are in danger of missing our favourite TV programme. But while our daily routines rely on clocks that tell us the time, science is discovering that our well-being is influenced by a very different kind of timepiece. Circadian rhythms---the human body's own internal clock---have a powerful influence on our health and behaviour. _ are programmed from birth and control functions ranging from temperature and blood pressure to sleep patterns. In recent years researchers have also discovered that this built-in mechanism can influence everything from the way we react to medicines to how well we learn music. The latest example, from experts at Harvard University in the US, shows that the human body clock can even dictat...\n\nQ: According to the passage, when are people most quick-thinking?", "options": ["In the morning.", "Around midday.", "In the late afternoon.", "In the early evening."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1601, "question": "Taiwanese fishing boats that sailed to the Diaoyu Islands to protest Japan's \"purchase\" of part of the islands completed their voyage Tuesday morning and have set sail for home. Local media reported that the boats finished their protest at 9:15 a.m. and are expected to return to a port in northeast Taiwan's Yilan county at noon Wednesday. Although the boats originally numbered 75,they were joined at sea by other boats from different parts of Taiwan, raising the total number to about 100 vessels. Organizers said the voyage was made to protect Taiwanese fishing rights in nearby waters and to protest Japan's \"purchase\" of part of the Diaoyu Islands. The Japanese government announced a plan to \"purchase\" part of the islands earlier this month despite repeated protests from the Chinese governme...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["About 100 boats joined the original team later.", "Negotiation will bring both countries out of the conflict.", "Japan's exports to China totaled 78 billion U.S. dollars in 2011.", "Japan's \"purchase\" has cast a shadow on China-Japan export and import."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3036, "question": "Once upon a time a peacock and a tortoise became great friends. The peacock lived in a tree on the bank of the stream in which the tortoise had his home, and every day the peacock danced near the stream and displayed his gay plumage for the amusement of his friend. Unfortunately, one day a bird-catcher caught the peacock and was about to take him away to the market. The unhappy bird begged his captor to allow him to say goodbyeto his friend -- the tortoise. The bird-catcher agreed and took the peacock to the tortoise, who was greatly astonished when he saw his friend become a captive. The tortoise asked the bird-catcher to let the peacock go, but the bird-catcher laughed at his request, saying that was his livelihood. The tortoise then said, \"If I give you a handsome present, will you let ...\n\nQ: This passage is a   _  .", "options": ["joke", "fairy tale", "fable", "life story"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 416, "question": "Grown-ups are often surprised by how well they remember something they learned as children but have never practiced ever since. A man who has not had a chance to go swimming for years can still swim as well as ever when he gets back in the water. He can get on a bicycle after many years and still ride away. He can play catch and hit a ball as well as his son. A mother who has not thought about the words for years can teach her daughter the poem that begins \"Twinkle, twinkle, little star\" or remember the story of Cinderella or Goldilocks and the Three Bears. One explanation is the law of overlearning, which can be stated as follows: Once we have learned something, additional learning trials increase the length of time we will remember it. In childhood we usually continue to practice such sk...\n\nQ: What is the author's opinion on cramming?", "options": ["It leads to failure in college exams.", "It increases students' learning interest.", "It's possible to result in poor memory.", "It's helpful only in a limited way."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2381, "question": "I was in my third year of teaching writing at Ralph High School in New York, when one of my students,15-year-old Mikey,gave me a note from his mother.It explained his absence from class the day before: \"Dear Mr. McCort,Mikey's grandmother,who is eighty years of age,fell down the stairs from too much coffee and I kept Mikey at home to take care of her and his baby sister so I couldn't go to my job. Please excuse Mikey and he'll do his best in the future.P.S.His grandmother is OK.\" I had seen Mikey writing the note at his desk.I said nothing.Most parental-excuse note, I received were penned by my students.The writers of those notes didn't realize that honest excuse notes were usually dull: \"Peter was late because the alarm clock didn't go off.\" The students always said it was hard putting 20...\n\nQ: How did the author usually find out his students' parental-excuse notes were dishonest?", "options": ["They were written in dull words.", "They were more like stories than facts.", "He called their parents and found out the truth.", "The handwriting obviously looked like children's."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3002, "question": "Events Calendar TUESDAY Landscape Pests Learn to identify, control and prevent seasonal landscape-disease and landscape-pest problems at the workshop, 3:30 pm. - 5 pm. Tuesday at the US National Arboretum, 3501 New York Ave NE, Washington. $15; registration required. 202-245-4521 or www.usna.usda.gov. THROUGH AUGUST 3 Horticultural Art Watercolors, pen-and-ink drawings and colored-pencil pieces by the Brookside Gardens School of Botanical Art and Illustration will be on display at the exhibit Botanic 2007: The Art and Science of Plants at Brookside Gardens Visitors Center, 1800 Glenallan Ave, Wheaton, through Aug. 3. Free. 301-962-1400 or www.brooksidegardens.org. THROUGH SEPTEMBER 9 Botanical Art Visit Patterns in Nature, an exhibit by Amy Lamb featuring photographs of flowers, leaves and...\n\nQ: If you go to Botanic Garden Exhibit, you   _  .", "options": ["can enjoy drawings and coloured-pencil pieces", "can learn how to kill pests living on the plants", "can find displays of 20 botanic gardens across the country", "will enjoy the photographs of flowers and leaves"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 999, "question": "It'll be an ordinary morning,like all the others.But instead of being woken up by the buzzing of an alarm clock, you'll be roused by the smell of freshly made coffee,light entering your room as the curtains open automatically,and a gentle back massage provided by your high-tech bed. This is what a typical person's life will be like two decades from now,according to The Guardian. Want to know more? After you get up,your apartment will be like an electronic orchestra with you as the conductor.With simple moves of your hand and spoken instructions,you'll be able to control your apartment's temperature,humidity,music and lighting.You'll be able to look through the day's news on translucent screens while your breakfast waits for you in the automatic oven. As you move into your kitchen,maybe you...\n\nQ: Which best describes the author's attitude toward our future lives?", "options": ["Objective", "Worried", "Skeptical", "Negative"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1986, "question": "Shakespeare's Sister Let us imagine, since facts are so hard to come by, what would have happened had Shakespeare had a wonderfully gifted sister, called Judith. Shakespeare himself went, very probably -- his mother was an heiress -- to the grammar school, where he may have learnt Latin -- Ovid, Virgil and Horace -- and the elements of grammar and logic. He was, it is well known, a wild boy who poached rabbits, perhaps shot a deer, and had, rather sooner than he should have done, to marry a woman in the neighborhood, who bore him a child rather quicker than was right. That escapade sent him to seek his fortune in London. He had, it seemed, a taste for the theatre; he began by holding horses at the stage door. Very soon he got work in the theatre, became a successful actor, and lived at the...\n\nQ: Why did Judith commit suicide to end her life?", "options": ["The fat manager rejected her and even insulted her.", "She married the wrong person and couldn't face it.", "She couldn't tolerate the violence of the poet's heart.", "She was caught between her ideal and the reality."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1732, "question": "A growing number of workers at Google Inc., Facebook Inc. and other employers are trading in their sit-down desks for standing ones, saying they feel more comfortable and energized. They also are _ by medical reports saying that sitting for too long leads to increased health risks. A standing desk sits high off the floor so a worker can either stand at it or sit on a high stool to use it. Officials at Palo Alto-based Facebook say a number of employees asked about standing desks after news articles were published about the health risks of sitting all day. The stories cited medical studies that tied excessive sitting to increased obesity and other health problems because of factors including a drop in physical activity. A 2010 study by the American Cancer Society found that women who sat mor...\n\nQ: The passage mainly talks about  _  .", "options": ["sitting for too long leads to increased health risks", "standing desks have replaced sit-down ones in Facebook Inc.", "more and more workers choose standing desks instead of sit-down ones", "many employees at Google opt for standing desks"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2848, "question": "Daniel Brown was just five years old when he climbed into the family car and let it roll away down the road. He was only three when he flooded the kitchen. His mother, Angela Brown is very busy looking after her new baby, a little girl called Laura, as well as Daniel. She told us, \"Daniel is so full of curiosity .\" At that moment, we hear a loud noise and then silence. We go upstairs and find Daniel getting out of a wardrobe which he has pulled over onto the floor, with a book in his hand. \"It's for you, Mum,\" he says and looks up at his mum and smiles. Seven-year-old Daniel has a lovely face. He has golden hair, big brown eyes, and a friendly smile. I have to admit that Daniel doesn't look like a naughty boy. Angela told me all about it, \"Once I found him as he was about to put Jasper in ...\n\nQ: Why was Daniel going to put the dog in the washing machine?", "options": ["He hoped to punish the dog.", "He wanted to clean the dog.", "He intended to make trouble.", "He wished to draw his mother's attention."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1890, "question": "A brother and sister have been reunited after more than 60 years, thanks to a letter in the Welwyn and Hatfield Times. For years John Hannant Kept a photograph of his long-lost sister, hoping they would meet again. Margery, the eldest of the three children, had signed up to the Royal Air Force as part of the war effort, when John was still a baby. The family lost touch and as the decade s passed only a single letter gave a clue to her whereabouts. The clue was enough for a WHT reader to recognize Margery and put the family back in touch.. John, 67, had been searching for a long time and a friend suggested writing to the paper. \"That's the one that made it, the letter to the paper a few months age,\" he said. \"It's like a dream come true. The last time we ever heard from Margery was in 1953 ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that  _", "options": ["since 1953 Margery has come back home only once.", "Margery received only one letter from John.", "Margery does not care about her family.", "WHT refers to a newspaper."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 567, "question": "Opportunity knocked on my door last January when I was given a chance to work in another country. At first, it seemed really scary for me to live on my own. But I had to overcome the true challenge! Luckily, I met seven new friends, six boys and one girl. They were really nice and I loved their company. We hung out most weekends. We cooked, watched movies, chatted and shared jokes! It was amazing -- until something unexpected happened ! One of my friends was diagnosed with kidney stones which needed to be removed as soon as possible. But our friend could not afford the surgery. He tried to get help from our other friends but they refused him. My heart cried for him! Our friends abandoned him just when he needed them most. I didn't know how to help him because I didn't have any money either...\n\nQ: Which of the following words can be used to describe the author?", "options": ["Warm - hearted.", "Adventurous.", "Open-minded.", "Clever."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 293, "question": "The Queen's English is now sounding less upper-class, a scientific study of the Queen's Christmas broadcasts has found. Researchers have studied each of her messages to the Commonwealth countries since 1952 to find out the change in her pronunciation from the noble Upper Received to the Standard Received. Jonathan Harrington, a professor at Germany's University of Munich, wanted to discover whether accent changes recorded over the past half century would take place within one person. \"As far as I know, there just is nobody else for whom there is this sort of broadcast records,\" he said. He said the noble way of pronouncing vowels had gradually lost ground as the noble upper-class accent over the past years. \"Her accent sounds slightly less noble than it did 50 years ago. But these are very...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about?", "options": ["The changes in a person's accent.", "The Queen's Christmas speeches on TV.", "The relationship between accents and social classes.", "The recent development of the English language."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2092, "question": "When George was thirty-five, he bought a small plane and learned to fly it. He soon became very good and made his plane do all kinds of tricks . George had a friend, whose name was Mark. One day George offered to take Mark up in his plane. Mark thought, \" I've traveled in a big plane several times, but I've never been in a small one, so I'll go. \" They went up, and George flew around for half an hour and did all kinds of tricks in the air. When they came down again, Mark was glad to be back safely, and he said to his friend in a shaking voice, \"Well , George, thank you very much for those two trips in your plane.\" George was very surprised and said, \" Two trips? \" \" Yes, my first and my last. \" answered Mark....\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is false?", "options": ["George learned to fly a plane very quickly .", "It took George a short time to learn to fly a plane.", "George had some difficulty learning to fly a plane.", "Mark decided to fly in George's small plane."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 244, "question": "As many people hit middle age, they often start to notice that their memory and mental attention are not what they used to be. We suddenly can't remember where we put the keys just a moment ago, or an old friend's name, or the name of an old band we used to love. It happens to most of us, but is it unavoidable? Scientists are increasingly showing that there's actually a lot that can be done. It turns that the brain needs exercise in much the same way as our muscles do, and the right mental workouts can improve our basic cognitive functions. Now, a new San Francisco Web-based company has taken it a step further and developed the first \"brain training program\" designed to actually help people improve and regain their mental sharpness. Called Lumosity, it was designed by some of the leading e...\n\nQ: The author explains the training results by  _", "options": ["making a comparison.", "presenting training findings.", "analyzing facts.", "setting down rules."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 27, "question": "Very soon the Rabbit noticed Alice, as she went hunting about, and called out to her, \"What are you doing out here? Run home this moment, and fetch me a pair of gloves and a fan! Quick, now!\" Alice was so much frightened that she ran off at once in the direction it pointed to. She saw a little house, on the door of which was a plate with the name \"W. RABBIT\". She went in and hurried upstairs. By this time she had found her way into a tidy little room with a table in the window, and on it a fan and two or three pairs of tiny white kid gloves: she took up the fan and a pair of the gloves, and was just going to leave the room, when her eye fell upon a little bottle that stood near the looking-glass. There was no label this time with the words' DRINK ME,' but she opened it and put it to her li...\n\nQ: The passage may come from a(an)   _  .", "options": ["science book", "wildlife magazine", "guide book", "English novel"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 52, "question": "\"What is the most important thing you've done in your life?\" The question was put to me during a presentation I gave to a group of lawyers. The answer came to me in an instant. It's not the one I gave, because the situation was not right. As a lawyer in the entertainment industry, I knew the audience wanted to hear some amusing stories about my work with well-known people, but here's the true answer: The most important thing I've ever done occurred on October 8,1990. I began the day playing tennis with an old friend I hadn't seen for a while. Between points we talked about what had been happening in each other's lives. He and his wife had just had a baby boy, who was keeping them up at night. While we were playing, a car came screaming up the road toward the courts. It was my friend's fath...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the author's description of the scene at the hospital?", "options": ["He found out that he was in the way.", "He would have felt guilty if he had not been there.", "He regretted that he went too late.", "His friend would have felt better if he had not been there."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1231, "question": "When your pet has an emergency, first aid is not a _ for veterinary treatment. However, before you are able to get your pet to a veterinarian , knowing some basic first aid can help. Bite Wounds Approach the pet carefully to avoid getting bitten. Wear a mask for the animal and then check the wound. Clean the wound with large amounts of saline . If these are not available, then regular water may be used. Wrap large open wounds to keep them clean. Bleeding Apply firm, direct pressure over the bleeding area until the bleeding stops. Hold the pressure for at least 10 minutes. Avoid bandages that cut off circulation. _ Check to see if the animal is choking on a foreign object. If an animal is not breathing, place it on a firm surface with its left side up. Check for a heartbeat. If you hear a h...\n\nQ: If your pet is burned by chemicals, you should  _  .", "options": ["wash away the chemicals with saline", "put an ice pack directly on the skin", "bind up the cut with a bandage", "get rid of them before washing"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2431, "question": "Big Brothers Big Sisters is based on the simplicity and power of friendship. It is a program which provides friendship and fun by matching _ (ages 7-17) with a volunteer adult who can be both a role model and a supportive friend. Volunteer tutors come from all walks of life--married, single, with or without children. Big Brothers and Big Sisters are not replacement parents or social workers. They are tutors: someone to trust, to have fun with, to talk and go to when needed. A Big Sister and Little Sister will generally spend between one and four hours together three or four times each month for at least twelve months. They enjoy simple activities such as a picnic at a park, cooking, playing sport or going to a football match. These activities improve the friendship and help the young perso...\n\nQ: According  to  Emily's  mother,  this  program  may  provide  Emily  with  _  .", "options": ["a new way to assess herself", "advice from her teachers", "a new way to judge her schoolmates", "more comments from her schoolmates"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1526, "question": "The atmosphere and oceans are not the only parts of the environment being damaged. Rain forests are being quickly destroyed as well, and their survival is questionable. E.O. Wilson, a biologist at Harvard, called the depletion of rain forest areas \"the greatest extinction since the end of the age of dinosaurs\". Unlike some environmental issues, rain forest depletion has fortunately received significant public and media attention. Despite the opposition to the cutting down of rain forests, the problem continues. Every year, Brazil chops down an area of forest the size of the state of Nebraska. In addition to the Amazon's rain forests, many other forests are being cut down as well. In Indonesia, Zaire, Papua-new Geinea, Malaysia, Burma, the Philippines, Peru, Colombia, Bolivia, and Venezuela...\n\nQ: This passage mainly tells us   _  .", "options": ["that limiting population growth is the primary step to solve all the environment problems.", "a serious fact that the rain forests are being destroyed every year, and the reason for that.", "about 25- 50 million acres of rain forests are destroyed each year.", "the growing population is not the real cause of the environment problem."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 37, "question": "A rare butterfly has been discovered in Britain for the first time in 60 years,having moved from Eastern Europe.The only previous record of a wild yellow-legged Tortoiseshell in Britain was in 1953,when it was seen just once in Sevenoaks,Kent.Several weeks ago,there were already four confirmed sightings,along the East coast in Norfolk,Suffolk and Kent,and six further reports of the butterfly in coastal areas. Conservationists are very excited about the sightings,which are rare in the butterfly world. The butterflies are thought to have flown on easterly winds across Europe in the last few weeks.The large and colourful insect mainly lives in Eastern Europe.In recent years,it has spread into Scandinavia and its number increases rapidly during warm weather.Also known as the Scarce Tortoiseshe...\n\nQ: The annual Big Butterfly Count is Intended to  _  .", "options": ["inspire amateurs'studying interest", "teach people to do good gardening", "study butterflies across Britain", "celebrate naturalists'contributions"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1854, "question": "Treetops, the hotel in the trees, are famous in the world. People know little about Kenya, but they know of Treetops. When King George VI died, Princess Elizabeth was staying on the Treetops, and when she came down from there, \"She _ him as the queen of the country\". The hotel is in the middle of the forest, and it shows the pleasure of Africa. When you visit it, you will be sent into the heart of the forest by hotel buses, and then a guide, with a gun to protect you against big game, will go with you to the Treetops. Before and after dinner, for the whole night if you wish, you can sit on the corridor , watching animals come to the water pool. The earliest hotel Treetops was built round a large tree on the opposite side of the water, but that was destroyed by fire and the new hotel Treeto...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that the guests   _  .", "options": ["will be protected by a guide in the forest", "can play with the cat-like animals", "can have parties in the dinning room", "could not sit on the corridor at night"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2203, "question": "'Well,' began Enfield, 'I was coming home about three o'clock on a black winter morning, when suddenly I saw two people. The first was a short man who was walking along the street, and the second was a little girl who was running as fast as she could. Well, the two bumped into each other and the child fell down. Then a terrible thing happened. The man calmly walked all over the child's body with his heavy boots, and left her screaming on the ground. It was an inhuman thing to do. I ran after the man, caught him and fetched him back. There was already a small crowd around the screaming child. The man was perfectly cool, but he gave me a very evil look, which made me feel sick in my stomach. The child's family then arrived, and also a doctor. The child had been sent to fetch the doctor for a...\n\nQ: The cheque was written by   _  .", "options": ["Mr. Utterson, an upright lawyer", "Mr. Jekyll, a well-known doctor", "Doctor Lanyon, Mr. Jekyll's friend", "Mr. Hyde, the short man mentioned in the passage above"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2148, "question": "Many parents watch the news or other shows as children play nearby. But new research shows that even when the television is just background noise,it may be to a child's normal development. It's estimated that 75 percent of very young children in the United States live in homes where the television is on most of the time,even though the kids often aren't watching it. The University of Massachusetts researchers recently studied how TV background noise might affect young children. The study looked at 50 1,2and 3yearolds. Each child came to a lab with a parent and was allowed to play for an hour with various toys. For half the time,a television was on in the room,showing the adult game show as well as advertisements. During the other half hour,the TV was turned off. As expected,the children pa...\n\nQ: In the study,the children   _   .", "options": ["were all 3yearolds", "were asked to watch adult TV shows", "played for an hour while the TV was on", "played with more than one toy"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3449, "question": "It's likely that everything you learned about America's ancient history is wrong. The new book,1491, completely changes our understanding of the America before the arrival of Columbus in 1492. DID YOU KNOW? When Columbus landed there were probably more people in the Americas than there were in Europe. The peoples of North America had such healthy life-styles that as late as the 19th century they continued to be the tallest people on earth. Facts have shown that the Americas were populated as long as 33,000 years ago. 4,000 years ago Mesoamerican farmers developed corn in a feat of genetic engineering that still isn't completely understood. COMMENTS ON 1491 \"In the tradition of Jared Diamond & John MePhee, a totally new view of pre-Columbian America\". -Richard Rhodes \"Attractively written a...\n\nQ: On the whole,1491 is a book mainly about America's  _  .", "options": ["life-styles", "population", "history", "agriculture"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 231, "question": "Nothing is more frustrating than not being able to sleep, tossing and turning . Your mind is racing, going over everything that happened that day. Night noises keep you awake. What can you do? Here are some things you can do to help you to fall asleep. Sleep only when sleepy This reduces the time you are awake in bed. If you can't fall asleep within 20 minutes, get up and do something boring until you feel sleepy. Don't expose yourself to bright light while you are up. The light tells your brain that it is time to wake up. Don't take naps This will ensure that you are tired at bedtime. If you just can't make it through the day without a nap, sleep less than one hour, and take a nap before 3 p.m. Get up and go to bed at the same time every day Even on weekends! When your sleep cycle has a r...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["You should follow the routine even on weekends.", "Go to bed right after you take a hot bath.", "The time to take exercise is important.", "Don't take a long nap even though you are very sleepy."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1360, "question": "A father with Parkinson's disease was arrested as he watched the Olympic cycling road race because he failed to smile or look as if he was enjoying himself. Mark Worsfold, a martial arts trainer and former soldier, claims that he was thrown to the floor and handcuffed just as cyclists passed by. His worried wife Nicola only found out he was being held after she reported him missing when he did not turn up for their daughter's ninth birthday party. The 54-year-old man had his fingerprints, DNA and _ taken before being questioned about why he did not appear to be enjoying the event on July 28. Police said Mr. Worsfold, who was held for over five hours, was arrested because of his manner, his state of dress and his being too near to the course. A spokesman added that the arrest was necessary ...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["The officers must have been punished for Worsfold' arrest.", "Worsfold has an expressionless face and probably looks strong.", "The officers apologized to Worsfold after one day's arrest.", "Worsfold was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease four years ago."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3441, "question": "Nickname: Hawaii's Island of Adventure Size: 4,028 square miles Population: 148,677. The most heavily populated areas are Hilo on the east side and Kailua-Kona on the west. Temperature: Averages between 71degFand 77degF year around ( _ ). Beaches: 47 Golf Courts: 20 Highest Peak: Mauna Kea, 13,796 feet. Agriculture: The bulk of Hawaii's farming products are grown and processed on the Big Island, including coffee, macadamia nuts and papaya. Lodging: 9,655 rooms total; nightly rates range from $35-$5,000. Airports: Hilo International Airport on the east side and Kona International Airport on the west side. Rental Cars: All of the nationally known rental car companies have locations at Hilo International and Kona International Airports as well as many resorts. In addition, Hilo, Kona and the ...\n\nQ: The average population per square mile on the island is about   _  .", "options": ["28", "32", "37", "44"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2698, "question": "BERLIN---A German woman, fearful that a burglar was trying to break into her second -storey apartment, called police after she heard someone climbing up to her balcony shortly after midnight, police said Thursday. Police discovered the \"burglar\" was a man carrying flowers and a bottle of wine who turned out to be the woman's boyfriend. But then arrested him on an outstanding reason. \"He was trying to surprise her with the flowers and a bottle of wine but it all went wrong,\" said Korbach police spokesman Volker Koenig. He said the man jumped down from the balcony and tried to escape but was quickly caught by police. \"He gave the police who were taking him to jail the bottle of wine as a gesture of thanks for the friendly treatment after the arrest. \" Koenig said. LONDON---A smoker who died ...\n\nQ: The public paid more attention to the smoker because   _  .", "options": ["he died after smoking for many years", "he had the sign put on his hearse and his grave", "he died of a lung disease without any treatment", "he wanted the sign left on his grave for one day"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3445, "question": "Study Books Basic Study Manual Hardcover :$ 37 Future success depends on the ability to learn. Here are the answers to the questions most often asked by parents, teachers, business trainers and by students themselves. Read this book and learn: What the three barriers to study are and what to do about them. What to do if you get tired of a subject you are studying. Twenty-six simple drills to help you learn how to study easily, rapidly and with full understanding. Buy and read Basic Study Manual and use it do dramatically improve your ability to study. Study Skills for Life Hardcover: $32 L. Ron Hubbard's study technology for children opens the door to their future success by giving them the ability to study and learn. Fully illustrated (,) for easy comprehension. Learning How to Learn Hard...\n\nQ: According to the advertisements, the four books are all intended for   _  .", "options": ["teachers", "children", "adults", "women"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 834, "question": "Homesick is a compound word made up of HOME and SICK.You know what each word means on its own, of course.But think about what the words mean when they are used together.Homesick means SICK FOR HOME. Now think for a minute about SEASICK.If you change the word home in the definition to the word sea, would the definition fit SEASICK? Seasick means SICK BY THE MOVEMENT ON THE SEA. When you are homesick ,the only place you want to be is at home.When you are seasick, the last place you want to be is at seA. Have you ever heard of a person being heartsick? Heartsick doesn't mean that something is wrong with a person's heart.people are heartsick when they are hurt deep inside and when they feel as if their hearts are broken. But, on the other hand, we have such compound words as handshake, handsta...\n\nQ: \"The last place you want to be\" is  _  .", "options": ["where you want to be most", "where you want to be least", "where you go the last", "the last place you go to"], "answer": 1}]